cimbbank.com.my 2012-05-25

# Welcome to CIMB

|  |  PRIVACY POLICY

WE FIRMLY BELIEVE THAT THE PRIVACY OF OUR CUSTOMERS' INFORMATION IS FUNDAMENTAL TO SECURING PUBLIC TRUST AND CONFIDENCE IN OUR PRODUCTS AND SERVICES AND THEREFORE, IT IS OUR POLICY TO RESPECT, MAINTAIN, PROTECT AND SAFEGUARD, AT ALL TIMES, THE PRIVACY OF OUR (CIMB BANK BERHAD (13491-P)/CIMB ISLAMIC BANK BERHAD (671380-H)) CUSTOMER’S INFORMATION.  

  1. **Our Commitment To Your Privacy**

We have always considered our customers and their interests as being of utmost priority in the provision of our products and services. For this reason and others, we are committed to ensuring that the privacy of your personal, banking and financial information as well as any other information in respect of or pertaining to the same ("Information") which you have disclosed, shared, exchanged or otherwise provided to us is at all times respected, maintained, protected and safeguarded.

Pursuant thereto and for your benefit, this Privacy Policy (which we may amend from time to time) is designed to explain and elaborate upon some of our policies and principles pertaining to the privacy of your Information, all of which we have adopted as a sign of our commitment to respecting, maintaining, protecting and safeguarding the privacy of your Information.

This Policy shall apply to all customers, visitors and users of CIMB’s websites and other electronic channels. The use of the term “We” and "CIMB" shall mean any company within the CIMB Group Sdn Bhd (“CIMB Group”) offering the products and services. 

This Website may contain references or hyperlinks to other websites not operated by us. We are not responsible for the contents, or the privacy practices, of these websites. In the event you choose to use links displayed on this web site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies published on those sites.

  2. **Types Of Information Which We Collect**

The types of Information, which we collect varies depending upon how you access and use our products and services. Nevertheless, the Information, which we collect generally comprises of data and information pertaining to yourself such as your name, address, e-mail address (or other contact information), age, gender, race, National Registration Identification Card (NRIC) number as well as other financial and banking information such as your bank balance, bank transactions, assets, liabilities, income and creditworthiness, and where the customer is a company, information pertaining to its assets, liabilities, directors, officers, shareholders and financial and commercial dealings. We may, at any point, request other related information from you to enable us to serve you better.

Please be aware that the user name you choose, the e-mail address you provide and any other information you enter may render you personally identifiable, and may possibly be displayed on this web site intentionally (based on choices you make during the registration process, or the configuration of the services or the web site ) or unintentionally (subsequent to a successful act of intrusion by a third party).

Your visit to this web site may be subject to the use of cookies to to gather enhance your user experience -- to remember your personal settings, or to use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to for general analysis of visitors and usage patterns. Cookies are small bits of information that are automatically stored on a person's web browser in their computer that can be retrieved by this Website. Should you wish to disable these cookies you may do so by changing the setting on your browser. However, you will be unable to enter certain part(s) of this Website.

  3. **Use Of The Information**

The Information, which we gather from you is intended to be used in the ordinary course of our business including the provision of our products and services to you as requested. However, our use of your Information may also extend to other purposes, among others, to enforce or defend any of our rights, to comply with all applicable legislation, laws and regulations, to enhance the quality of our products and services, to prevent fraud or illegal activities, to prepare demographics concerning our customers' use of our products and services as well as to offer additional products or services that we believe may be of benefit to you,at our sole discretion, be made available to our third party vendors, advertisers, affiliates or relevant third parties in aggregate or demographic form. 

  4. **Employees' Access to the Information**

We repeat our commitment to respect, maintain, protect and safeguard the privacy of your Information by ensuring that employees’ access to the Information which you have disclosed, shared, exchanged or otherwise provided to us is limited to authorised employees who are fully trained and well-equipped to handle your Information. Each of our said authorised employees are required to adhere to our commitment herein specifically our dedication to safeguarding the privacy of your Information at all times. Failure by our respective authorized employees herein to comply with the same and generally the terms of this Privacy Policy shall be met with the necessary disciplinary action. 

  5. **Security Measures Employed to Safeguard the Privacy of the Information**

It is our policy to ensure that adequate and stringent security controls, measures and protocols are employed to safeguard the privacy of your Information, all of which shall continue even after whatever contractual relationship between you and us has come to an end. While we shall use our best efforts to ensure that the privacy of all Information is kept secure, please note that it is an accepted fact that no data transmission conducted over the Internet and/or through other electronic channels can be guaranteed to be wholly secure. Further thereto, we shall neither be held responsible nor liable for any damages or losses which you may suffer, whether directly or indirectly, as a result of the said Information being stolen, tampered with, copied, abused, misused or otherwise violated. 

Further information on the security controls, measures and protocols, which we have employed herein are specified and elaborated upon in our SECURITY ARRANGEMENT, which may be read at [www.cimbclicks.com.my.](http://www.cimbclicks.com.my/)

  6. **Sharing of Information**

In view of our strict compliance to the Banking and Financial Institution Act (BAFIA)/ Islamic Banking Act, we do not disclose your Information to any third party or external organization unless you have consented to such disclosure. To help us to serve you better and to keep you informed of the latest marketing and promotional offers we feel would be useful and beneficial to you, your name, contact particulars and/or non-financial information may, from time to time, be provided to (i) any company within the CIMB Group residing, situated, carrying on business, incorporated or constituted within Malaysia; and (ii) any other third parties (including CIMB Group’s affiliates, third party vendors and advertisers) within or outside Malaysia and any company within the CIMB Group residing, situated, carrying on business, incorporated or constituted outside Malaysia, where expressly consented to by you. 

Where such information is provided to any company within the CIMB group and/or third parties, where you had consented to the above disclosure, we shall endeavour to ensure that they comply with the same standard regulating the privacy of your Information as that which is imposed by us. If you do not want your name, contact particulars and/or non-financial information being further disclosed to any company within the CIMB Group or the said third parties for the purposes of cross-selling and/or you do not want to be contacted by us or the said third parties for the sale or promotion of any products or services via the posting of any promotional and/or marketing materials, please notify us accordingly via electronic-mail or by calling our Call Center at the email address or telephone number specified in item 9 below or by writing in to RB-Direct Marketing, Level 26, Menara Bumiputra-Commerce, 11, Jalan Raja Laut, 50350, Kuala Lumpur, (Ref: Privacy). Please allow 1 to 2 weeks for your request to take effect. In any communication channel chosen by you to notify us of your decision, please specify your name as per IC, New IC/ Old IC/ Passport number. Should you thereafter at any time decide to receive our promotional and/or marketing materials, simply call any of our officers at our Call Center and we will gladly assist you with your request. 

Notwithstanding the generality of this Privacy Policy and while we shall, at all times, endeavour to safeguard the privacy of your Information, we may nevertheless disclose your Information to other third parties where such disclosure:-

|  | is requested or authorised by you;   
---|---  
| is used for the purpose of completing, verifying or restricting any transaction made by you;   
| is made to the Central Credit Unit established by Bank Negara Malaysia pursuant to its request;   
| is lawfully permitted or required;   
| is in compliance with any judicial order or legal requirement;   
| is required to protect and defend us and our property; and   
| is required to protect the interests of the public including but not limited to the detection of crimes and the apprehension of criminals.   
  7. **Customer's Choices in Respect of the Provision of the Information**

While you are neither bound nor obligated to provide us with any of your Information, your choice not to do so (whether due to your disagreement with the methods employed by us to safeguard the privacy of your Information or otherwise) may result in you being prohibited from accessing or making full use of our products and services, neither of which shall render us responsible or liable for. 

  8. **Accuracy of the Information**

Please note that the accuracy of your Information provided to us is essential, among others, to provision of our products and services to you. It is therefore a term and condition governing the provision of our products and services that you undertake to ensure the accuracy, completeness and currency of all Information which you disclose, share, exchange or otherwise provide to us by updating and notifying the Bank in writing or by such other means the Bank deems acceptable of any changes in the Information.

Should you also have any other queries concerning your Information, please contact our Call Centre or e-mail us, at the contact number and address as specified under Item 9 below. 

  9. **Questions about this Privacy Policy**

Should you also have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact our Call Centre or e-mail us, at the contact number and address as specified below:

CIMB Bank Call Center  
10th Floor, Menara Atlas, Plaza Pantai  
No. 5, Jalan 4/83a, Off Jalan Pantai Baru  
59200 Kuala Lumpur  
Tel: +603 2295 6100  
Fax: +603 2288 1653 / +603 2288 1654   
E-mail: [callcenter@cimb.com](mailto:callcenter@cimb.com)

  10. **Website Links**

Please note that CIMB’s websites may contain hyperlinks to other websites not operated by us. A link to such websites is not an endorsement of the contents of such websites and we make no warranties as to the information contained in such websites. We are not responsible for the contents, or the privacy practices, of these websites.

  11. **Complaints Handling**

Complaints if any relating to any matter herein can be made and sent to the following address and/or by contacting us by telephone and/or facsimile at the following numbers:-

Customer Resolution Unit  
17th Floor, Menara Bumiputra Commerce  
11, Jalan Raja Laut  
50350 Kuala Lumpur  
Tel No: +603 2619 2380  
Fax No: +603 2691 3248  
E-mail: [CRU@cimb.com](mailto:CRU@cimb.com)

|  |   
---
